The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
As expected of Master !
I can't believe you managed to hide like this.
master of this move.
Is this thing also a Celestial Beast Feed ?
I'm unsure who is eating whom...
I can handle a few Celestial Beast Feeds
but this one is terrifying.
I must not disturb it.
This is...
a celestial restriction ?
This is bad !
These Celestial Beast Feeds don't have a Divine Sense,
they can only act on sight.
I should be able to hide.
As expected !
We made it out of there
thanks to the wandering souls.
Fellow cultivator,
I'm afraid we are the only 2 people
remaining in the Celestial Beast Temple.
Since this place is already collapsing,
why did fellow cultivator come find me
instead of looking for a way out ?
Fellow cultivator doesn't have to worry.
My name is Sun Lei.
You must have seen
what happened just now.
I'm not afraid to tell you
that I'm not really from the Da Lou Sword Sect.
I infiltrated the sect
to kill and steal treasures.
If fellow cultivator takes one more step, I will have to act.
This person is only Early stage Soul Formation
but his Divine Sense is very powerful.
If I specifically didn't know a technique
to detect Divine Sense,
I would not have been able to notice him following us.
I know !
He must be hiding his cultivation.
Fellow cultivator,
I won't beat around the bush,
there are 3 treasures in this cave.
The first is a celestial jade
the second is celestial metal,
the third is a celestial sword.
How many
did you obtain ?
They came back too fast,
so I didn't get any.
It's hard to predict what will happen,
I'd rather be with him to take the treasures.
When facing the Celestial Beast Feeds,
I will still have a chance to kill him.
Fellow cultivator,
the celestial jade has been condensing
celestial spiritual energy for thousands of years
and is considered priceless.
My guess is that
the celestial metal
it's a type of defensive artifact.
And the most precious thing
is the celestial sword.
There are many Celestial Beast Feeds
so it will be hard to get the 3 treasures.
Why don't you and I work together ?
Oh ? And why should I help you ?
I only want the celestial sword.
The other two
will belong to you.
How is that ?
I don't want the celestial sword.
And I'm not interested
in the other 2 treasures either.
Fellow cultivator, what do you want ?
If he wasn't hiding his cultivation,
I would have already killed him
to prevent future troubles.
Fellow cultivator Sun,
You want me to risk my life to help you get the celestial sword
for just 2 items that might not even be obtainable ?
Do you think I'm 3 years old ?
What do you want ?
I noticed that when you arrived,
you guys were able to detect the spacial rifts
before they even appeared…
Full Search Tactic,
it's a technique of the Da Lou Sword Sect.
It's not a problem
to gift it to you.
Fellow cultivator is indeed quick on his decisions.
I won't beat around the bush anymore,
I want that gourd
in your Third Senior's bag.
Then I’ll be willing to take this risk with you.
Fellow cultivator, don't make it hard for me.
This gourd
is the reason why I infiltrated the Da Lou Sword Sect.
If fellow cultivator helps me get the celestial sword,
Purification wood
I will give you a piece of purification wood.
Although it isn’t as good as the gourd,
it can also absorb celestial spiritual energy.
Fellow cultivator, lead the way.
That black beast feed
must have devoured that skeleton.
It was nourished by the celestial artifacts
and it gained its own domain.
The reason why there are so many Celestial Beast Feeds
is that they must all be its offspring.
To get the treasures,
we must reduce their numbers.
Fellow cultivator,
I’ll lure them out with a technique.
Then we
kill an many of them as we can.
Once the black one moves
we'll run away immediately
and meet back where we met.
A Thunder Toad !
Let's start.
Nine-colored Rainbow Smoke,
Go !
Fellow cultivator,
together
we can beat any amount of beast feeds !
Here it comes !
This is bad,
I'm running out of spiritual energy.
If he acts now,
it's over for me.
Brother Sun was not where we agreed to meet
but it turns out you're injured.
In that case,
please continue to cultivate
while I protect you.
He faced the black beast feed
and was unharmed.
This person's cultivation
is enigmatic.
Fellow cultivator, lets go back.
Today, I will definitely kill that beast feed
to avenge my finger.
Bastard, come out !
Sun Lei's Origin Soul\NDa Lou Sword Sect
Fellow cultivator,
this spell has a time limit.
It will only last 10 breaths.
I will go get the treasures first
and then come to save you.
Fellow cultivator Sun,
you haven't given me the purification wood yet.
Why are you in such a hurry ?
If we fight now,
when the Celestial Beast Feeds come back,
I may not survive.
The sword is protected by celestial restrictions.
Even with my Master's jade,
I need to take it slow.
A normal cultivator
will die if he attempts to break it.
Although this restriction is exquisite,
it's not unbreakable.
This...this...
Master's artifact
can freeze everything for 10 breaths.
Yet it only lasted 8 breaths !?
That bastard !
All of this scheming
was in vain.
Let's...
die together !
Explode !
This is...
spacial rifts ?
Master,
this place is collapsing !
It's collapsing ! It's collapsing !
Not just the cave
but this whole Celestial Realm fragment is collapsing !
Falling from the night sky and melting into dust\Nlike water without a source.
Like the difference between clouds and mud,\Nthe truth cannot be found in conflict.
Life and death\Nare like the moment when the rain falls
and like many other unseparable things.
In this lifetime,\Nto cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled\Nbecause half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate\Nto ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage\Nto pierce the heart and the soul
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend down can you understand\Nthe hidden edge of the blade.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers\Nwhile prosperity sprouts in summer.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,\Nthe law of cause and effect.
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.\NReincarnation is not to be feared.